<speak>
    Regret.<break time="2000ms"/>
    I have no regrets about leaving.<break time="1000ms"/>
    I regret having to leave so early.<break time="1000ms"/>
    We regret that we cannot accept your invitation.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Attend.<break time="2000ms"/>
    It's unlikely that she will attend.<break time="1000ms"/>
    We attend the same church.<break time="1000ms"/>
    It is logical to assume that they will attend.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Propensity.<break time="2000ms"/>
    He had a propensity for crime.<break time="1000ms"/>
    She's inherited from her father a propensity to talk too much.<break time="1000ms"/>
    The criminal propensities of the family extended over several generations.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Lurch.<break time="2000ms"/>
    The train gave a violent lurch.<break time="1000ms"/>
    The ship suddenly lurched to the left.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Jane has a natural lurch for learning, and it comes easy for her.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Perennial.<break time="2000ms"/>
    Flooding is a perennial problem for people living by the river.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Teddy bears are a perennial favorite with children.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Lack of resources has been a perennial problem since the beginning.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Astray.<break time="2000ms"/>
    The older boys led him astray.<break time="1000ms"/>
    It's easy to be led astray by the reports in the papers.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Facet.<break time="2000ms"/>
    He studied every facet of the question.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Light reflected from myriads of facets of hoar frost.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Each facet of the problem requires careful attention.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Imbue.<break time="2000ms"/>
    A feeling of optimism imbues her works.<break time="1000ms"/>
    All his poetry is imbued with such emotions.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Her training at the school for the deaf imbued her with a sense of purpose that she had never known before.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Steady.<break time="2000ms"/>
    There was a steady rain all day.<break time="1000ms"/>
    He finally has a steady job.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Slow and steady wins the race.<break time="1000ms"/>
    
    Debris.<break time="2000ms"/>
    Debris in the street made the going difficult.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Everything was covered by dust and debris.<break time="1000ms"/>
    Forensic experts carried out a painstaking search of the debris.<break time="1000ms"/>
</speak>